name: 'Common Verbs'
questions:
  -
    question: '$ TV'
    answers:
      - watch
      - 'listen to'
      - see
    correct: 1
  -
    question: '$ Spanish'
    answers:
      - live
      - have
      - study
    correct: 3
  -
    question: '$ magazines'
    answers:
      - read
      - go
      - watch
    correct: 1
  -
    question: '$ children'
    answers:
      - eat
      - have
      - drink
    correct: 2
  -
    question: '$ in a bank'
    answers:
      - work
      - live
      - have
    correct: 1
  -
    question: '$ to the radio'
    answers:
      - listen
      - watch
      - like
    correct: 1
  -
    question: '$ a new car'
    answers:
      - eat
      - 'listen to'
      - want
    correct: 3
  -
    question: '$ fast food'
    answers:
      - drink
      - eat
      - read
    correct: 2
  -
    question: '$ coffee'
    answers:
      - eat
      - drink
      - read
    correct: 2
  -
    question: '$ English'
    answers:
      - speak
      - watch
      - work
    correct: 1
  -
    question: '$ in an apartment'
    answers:
      - like
      - love
      - live
    correct: 3
  -
    question: '$ dogs'
    answers:
      - like
      - live
      - speak
    correct: 1
